Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), Hudson Valley Area Joint Board; Records apap050
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, 1919-1989; 8.19 cubic ft.
  - Local Files, 1950-1990; Undated; 5.4 cubic ft.
    - Local 1032, Prince High Rock Mills, Contracts, ca. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Local 1032, Prince High Rock Mills, Contracts, 1964; 1966; 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Local 1032, Printex Corporation, By-Laws, 1958-1966; 1972; 1974; 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Local 1122, Correspondence with Board, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Local 1122, Elite Manufacturing Co., Contracts, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Local 1122, Faith Mills Corp, Contracts, 1958; 1960; 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Local 1122, Meeting Minutes, 1959-1962; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Local 1246, Charter, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Local 1246, Hudson Glue Corp., Contracts, 1958; 1960; 1962; 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Local 1246, Hudson Industries Corporations, Contracts, 1967-1968; 1970; 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Local 1246, Membership Minutes, 1951-1952; 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Local 1277, By-Laws, ca. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Local 1277, Insl-x, Contracts, 1957; 1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Local 1280, Berkshire Joint Board, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Local 1318, Lynrus Finishing Co., Contracts, 1965; 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Local 1318, Membership Meetings, 1958-1960; 1962; 1964; 1966; 1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Local 1318, Metroteze Inc, Contracts, 1956-1959; 1962; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Local 1338, Atlas Fiber Co. Inc, Contracts, 1958; 1960-1961; 1963; 1965; 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Local 1338, Atlas Fiber Co., Membership Minutes, 1958-1964; 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Local 1338, Mastercraft, Agreement, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Local 1338, Mastercraft, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Local 1338, Mastercraft Industries, Contracts, 1969-1970; 1973-1976; 1979; 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Local 1351, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Local 1351, Steiner, Contracts, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Local 1410, Skydyne Inc., Arbitration, 1960; 1956-1957; 1964-1966; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Local 1410, Skydyne Inc., By-Laws, 1958; 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Local 1410, Skydyne Inc., Contracts, (1 of 2), 1955-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Local 1410, Skydyne Inc., Contracts, (2 of 2), 1955-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Local 1410, Skydyne Newspaper Clippings, 1959; 1962 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Local 1420, Jack Barnett and Sons, Arbitration, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Local 1420, Jack Barnett Slipper, By-Laws, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Local 1420, Jack Barnett Slipper Co., Inc, Contracts, 1956-1957; 1959; 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Local 1420, Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Local 1456, Charter, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Local 1456, A &W, Arbitration, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Local 1456, A &W Products Co., Inc, Contracts, 1957; 1959; 1961; 1963; 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Local 1466, Crown Carton, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Local 1466, Crown Carton Inc.+, Contracts, 1958-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Local 1466, Membership Minutes, 1960; 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Local 1477, Vaucanson Silk Mills, Arbitration, 1954; 1959-1960; 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Local 1477, Vaucanson Silk Mills, Contracts, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Local 1477, Vaucanson Silk Mills, Meeting Minutes, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Local 1537, Ace Fibers Co., Contracts, 1966; 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Local 1537, Charter, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Local 1537, Go-Bar Footwear Co., Arbitration, 1964-1966; 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Local 1537, Go-Bar Footwear CD & Ace Fibre Mills Inc, By-Laws, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Local 1537, Go-Bar Footwear, Contracts, 1961; 1964-1966; 1968; 1970-1973; 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Local 1537, Minutes, 1964; 1966; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Local 1596, Inflated Products Inc., Arbitration, 1963; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Local 1596, Inflated Products Inc., By-Laws, ca.1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Local 1596, Inflated Products Inc., Contracts, 1963; 1965-1966; 1969; 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Local 1596, Inflated Products LeaFlets From Company, abt. Products, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Local 1596, Membership Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Local 1625, Change-O-Natic Corp., Contract, 1969-1970; 1972; 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Local 1625, International Cord and Thread and Change-O-Natic Corp., By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Local 1625, International Cord and Thread and Change-O-Natic, Minutes, 1964; 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Local 1625, International Cord and Thread, Charter, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Local 1625, International Cord and Thread, Corp., Contracts, 1962; 1964-1965; 1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Local 1648, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Local 1648, Carnegie Coating Company Inc., Charter, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Local 1648, Carnegie Coating Company Inc., Charter Applications, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Local 1648, Carnegie Coating Company Inc., Contracts, 1964-1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Local 1714, Empire State Bedding Co., Contracts, 1966; 1970; 1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Local 1714, Sealy of Eastern New York Inc., Agreement, 1976; 1979; 1982; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Local 1714, Sealy of Eastern New York Inc., By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Local 1714, Sealy of Eastern New York Inc., Contracts, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Local 1761, Bam Industries & Beaver Cloth, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Local 1761, Bam Industries Inc, Contracts, 1973; 1976-1978; 1981; 1984 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Local 1870, Academic Press Inc. & Johnson Reprint Corp., By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Local 1870, Academic Press, Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Local 1870, Academic Press Inc. & Johnson Reprint Co., Contracts, 1974; 1977; 1980; 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Local 1873, Futura Fabrics Corp., By-Laws, ca. 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Local 1873, Futura Fabrics Corp., Contracts, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Local 1916, Cryogenic Structures Corporation, Arbitration, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Local 1916, Cryogenic Structures Corporation, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Local 1916, Cryogenic Structures Inc., Contracts, 1974; 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Local 1916, Cryogenic Structures Inc., Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Local 1939, Fasco Coated Products Inc., Contracts, 1977; 1980; 1983; 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Local 1939, Packaging Lithographers, Contracts, 1972; 1975; 1978; 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Local 1939, Packaging Systems, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Local 1939, Packaging System Corp., Contracts, 1964; 1966; 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Local 1939-0, Ogden Allied Services Corp., Contracts, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Local 1946, Union Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Local 1946, X-Tyal International Corp., By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Local 1946, X-Tyal International Corp., Contracts, 1976-1980; 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Local 1946, X-Tyal Corporation, Minutes, 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Local 2317, Cohoes Sleeping Bag Co., 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Local 2317, Mohawk and Hudson River, Humane Society, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Local 2317, Universal Needle Craft Corporation, By-Laws, ca. 1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Local 2317, Universal Needle Craft Corporation, Contracts, 1976-1977; 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Local 2318, Hoerner Waldorf Bag, By-Laws, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Local 2318, Hoerner Waldorf Division, Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Local 2325, Industrial Knitted Fabrics and Finishing Corporation, Arbitration, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Local 2325, Industrial Knitted Fabrics and Finishing Corporation, By-Laws, ca. 1976; 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Local 2342, Union Keuffel & Esser Company, By-Laws, ca. 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Local 2342, Keuffel & Esser Company, Contracts, 1978; 1980-1981; 1983; 1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Local 2342, Keuffel & Esser Company, Court Case, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Local 2342, Keuffel & Esser Company, Newsletter, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Local Unknown, Albany Felt, Agreement, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Local Unknown, Anchor Aluminum Corp, Contract, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Local Unknown, Barry Pac Inc., Contracts, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Local Unknown, Cohoes Sleeping Bag Factory Inc., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Local Unknown, Agreement, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Local Unknown, Dutchness Industries Inc., Arbitration, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Local Unknown, Hanover Print Works Inc., Contracts, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Local Unknown, Industrial Knitted Fabrics and Finishing Corp., Contracts, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Local Unknown, J.J. O'Donnell Woolens Inc., Contracts, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Local Unknown, K & P Enterprises Inc., T/A Carnegie Industries, Contracts, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Local Unknown, Maybern Corp., Contracts, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Local Unknown, Mohawk & Hudson River Humane, Contract Society Inc, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Local Unknown, New Stan Dyeing and Finishing, Arbitration, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Local Unknown, Newburgh Weave Mills, Contracts, 1960; 1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Local Unknown, Park Tissue Paper, Newspaper Clippers, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Local Unknown, Troy Laundry, Contract, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Central Labor Union Councils - AFL-CIO, 1952-1979; .6 cubic ft.
    This series contains the records of central union councils affiliated with the AFL-CIO. The TWUA, which the Hudson Valley Area was a part of, joined the AFL-CIO around 1976. Prior to the formation of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, the Columbia County Joint Board held the records of the Upper Hudson Area Industrial Council, CIO. The Upper Hudson Area Industrial Council became the Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union, AFL-CIO in 1958. The records were then transfered from the Columbia County Joint Board to the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in 1958-1959. The Hudson Valley Area Joint Board also oversaw he records of the Central Labor Union of New York, AFL-CIO.
    - Central Labor Union of Newburgh, New York, Constitution and By-Laws, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Central Labor Union of Newburgh, New York, Minutes, 1960; 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - New York State Industrial Union Council, CI0, Constitution, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Attendance Books, 1959-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Constitutions, 1956; 1959; 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Correspondence, 1960; 1962; 1965-1966; 1980; 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Correspondence w/ Kingston Prof. Ffighters' Assoc., 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council Delegates List, 1980-1981; 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1958-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1958-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Meeting Notices, 1955-1963; 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Council AFL-CI0, Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Union Council, Telegrams, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Upper Hudson Area Industrial Union Council, Constitution and By-Laws, 1952; 1956; ca. 1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Upper Hudson Area Industrial Union Council, C10, Minutes, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Upper Hudson Area Industrial Union Council, News Releases, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Amsterdam Joint Board, 1946-1977; .8 cubic feet
  This series contains the records of the Amsterdam Joint Board which was chartered in 1942. The Amsterdam Joint Board joined the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in 1968. Included in the records are documents relating to the founding of the board and their bylaws and constitutions. The records also contain arbitration documents, constitutions, meeting minutes, and contracts of local chapters of the board.
  - By-Laws, 1956; 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local 1, Bigelow-Stanford, By-Laws, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local 1, Bigelow-Stanford, Contracts, 1948; 1950-1951; 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local 1, Stipulation, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local 489, By-Laws, 1948; 1959-1960; 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local 489, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 489, Farewell Party, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local 489, Meeting Minutes, 1966-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 489, Minutes of Executive Board Meetings, 1967-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local 489, Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 489, Mohasco Industries, Arbitration, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local 489, Mohasco Industries, Contracts, 1957-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local 489, Mohawk Carpet Mills, Agreement, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Local 489, Mohawk Carpet Mills, Arbitration (1 of 2), 1952; 1956; 1960; 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local 489, Mohawk Carpet Mills, Arbitration (2 of 2), 1952; 1956; 1960; 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 489, Mohawk Carpet Mills, Contracts, 1947-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 489, Mohawk Carpet Mills, Grievance In Twisting and Finishing Department, 1956; 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 489, Photographs, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local 646, Fownes Brothers, By-Laws, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local 646, Fownes Brothers, Contracts, 1946-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local 646, Fownes Brothers, Strike Authorization Form, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local 835, Chalmers Knitting Co., Contracts, 1946; 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local 835, Montco Manufacturing, Arbitration, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Local 835, Montco Manufacturing, By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Local 835, Montco Manufacturing Co., Contracts, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Local 856, Minutes, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Local 1761, Bam Industries, Contracts, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1964-1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Capital District Area Joint Board, 1919-1973; Undated; 1.8 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of the Capital District Area Joint Board. The Capital District Area Joint Board which was chartered in 1937, became a part of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in 1968. This series contains records of the main board, including meeting minutes, bylaws, and constitutions. The series also includes local chapter arbitration documents, meeting minutes, and bylaws. This series also contains records related to the Troy Area Industrial Union Council, CIO, which was associated with the Capital District Area Joint Board.
  - Ballston Spa Knitting, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Certificate for Twentieth Anniversary, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constitution, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - C10 Constitution and Handbook, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Regional Director of TWUA, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with State and Federal Legislators, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Decora Mills, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fuld & Hatch, 1941; 1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 577, Garnett Workers Union, Contracts, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - International Representative, Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - J.T Flagg Knitty Co., Contracts, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Labor Management Committee of The Troy Community Chest, Minutes, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Legislative, Meeting Minutes, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - List of Officers of The Joint Board and Local Unions, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local 89, Beaunit Mills Inc, Arbitrations, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local 89, Beaunit Mills, By-Laws, ca. 1950 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local 89, Beaunit Mills, Contracts, 1947-1949; 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Local 89, Beaunit Mills, Minutes, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Local 89, Beaunit Mills, Report on Weavers Workload Changes at Beaunit Mills, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Local 237, National Automotive Fibres Inc./National Automotive Wadding Co. Inc., NAFI Corp., By-Laws, ca. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Local 237, National Automotive Fibres Inc./National Automotive Wadding Co., Inc., NAFI Corp., Contracts, 1950-1951; 1953-1957; 1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Local 237, National Automotive Fibres Inc./National Automotive Wadding Co., Inc., NAFI Corp., Correspondence, 1949; 1951; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Local 237, National Automotive Fibres Inc./National Automotive Wadding Co., Inc., NAFI Corp., Minutes, 1946-1962 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Local 237, Waterford Industries, Contracts, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Local 238, Peerless Fibre Co., Contracts, 1949; 1952 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Local 238, Peerless Fibre, Minutes, 1946-1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Local 346, Cohoes Textile Printing Co., Contracts, 1948-1951; 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Local 346, Cohoes Textile Printing Co., Correspondence, 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Local 346, Cohoes Textile Printing Co., Minutes, 1946-1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Local 575, Cohoes Dye and Fishing Co., Contracts, 1948; 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Local 575, Cohoes Dye and Fishing Co., Minutes, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Local 574, Wilson Athletic Goods, Arbitration, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Local 574, Wilson Athletic Goods, Contracts, 1947; 1949-1950; 1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Local 574, Photographs, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Local 675, Wilson Bros, Contracts, 1947; 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Local 675, Wilson Bros, Minutes, 1943-1954 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Local 907, Regis Textiles Inc., Contracts, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Local 964, William Barnett and Son, By-Laws, ca. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Local 964, William Barnett and Son, Charter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Local 964, William Barnett and Son, Contracts, 1941-1966 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Local 964, William Barnett and Son, Minutes (1 of 2), 1940-1961 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Local 964, William Barnett and Son, Minutes (2 of 2), 1940-1961 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Local 976, Montagne Furniture Company, Albany Parlor Co., Charter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Local 976, Montagne Upholstering Company, By-Laws, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Local 976, Montagne Upholstering Company, Contracts, 1948-1964 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Local 976, Montagne Upholstering Company, Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Local 976, Montagne Upholstering Company, Minutes, 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Local 1351, Minutes, 1954-1956; 1965 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Local 1351, Star Textile & Research Inc., Agreement, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Local 1351, Star Textile & Research Inc., Contracts, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Local 1351, Star Woolen, Agreement and Contracts, 1954-1956; 1958; 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 1351, Star Woolen, Arbitration, 1957; 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 1351, Star Woolen, By-Laws, ca. 1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 1351, Star Woolen, Charter, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Marvin Neitzel Corporation, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1947-1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Report To TWUA, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Notices from the Joint Board, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Organizing Leaflets, 1953; 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Dated, 1945-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Identified, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Unidentified (1 of 2), Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Unidentified (2 of 2), Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sealy Mattress Company, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Star Woolen Company, 1947; 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Swan-Knit Company, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Telegrams, 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Affiliation Forms, ca. 1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, By-Laws, ca. 1950 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Constitution and By-Laws, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Correspondence, 1953; 1957-1958; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Meeting Notices, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Minutes (1 of 2), 1948-1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Minutes (2 of 2), 1948-1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Resolution Against UE, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Troy Area Industrial Union Council, Statement By Joseph Killian on Unemployment Insurance, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Troy Waste Manufacturing Company, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - TWUA Constitutions, 1946; 1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Columbia County Joint Board, 1938-1957; 1.44 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of the Columbia County Joint Board. The Columbia County Joint Board, which was chartered in 1947, merged with the Mid-Hudson Joint Board to form the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in 1957. Ths series contains the main board's meeting minutes, bylaws, and contracts, as well as arbitration documents, bylaws, and constitutions for the local chapters. This series also contains a scrapbook with newspapers and photographs of the board.
  - By-Laws, JT. Bd., 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [Columbia County] Joint Board, Minutes (1 of 2), 1948-1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - [Columbia County] Joint Board, Minutes (2 of 2), 1948-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local 96, A.D Juilliard & Co., Contracts, 1940-1941; 1948; 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local 96, By-Laws, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local 96, Minutes, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local 96, Naming Administrator for the local, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 96, Thermo Mills Inc., Contracts, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local 96, Wei-Sack Mills Inc., Contract, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 791, Arbitrations, Textiles By- Products, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local 791, Hand Prints, Contracts, 1950; 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 791, Minutes (1 of 2), 1951-1952; 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 791, Minutes (2 of 2), 1951-1952; 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 791, Textile By-Products, Contracts, 1943-1949; 1951-1953; 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 792, High Rock Knitting Co., Contracts, 1944-1946; 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local 792, High Rock Mills, Arbitration, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local 792, High Rock Mills, By-Laws, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local 792, High Rock Mills Inc., Contracts, 1951; 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local 792, Membership Minutes, 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local 792, Minutes Union Company Meetings, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Local 793, Minutes, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Local 793, Springdale Mills, Contract, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Local 793, Thermo Mills Inc., Contract, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Local 938, Contract, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Local 938, Nassau Pen, Contract, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Local 1122, Faith Mills, Contracts, ca. 1950 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Local 1246, Hudson Glue Corp., Contracts, 1946-1948; 1950-1953; 1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local 1342, Union Pye Works, Contract, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reports By Business Manager, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1938-1939; 1941; 1945-1951 (Oversized 2)